Guide to the Rice University Shell Center for Sustainability records, 2003-2017 UA 393
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Shell Center for Sustainability records
2003-2017
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Andre, Lilibeth
UA 393
7 Linear Feet 7 boxes
This collection contains the administrative files, meeting minutes and records, publications, audio/visual (DVDs) presentations, and reports for the Rice University Shell Center for Sustainability.
Historical Note
Rice University and Shell Oil Company launched the Shell Center for Sustainability (SCS) in 2002. The Center is housed in the School of Social Sciences and collaborates with other centers and institutes at Rice University. SCS works closely with schools and organizations within the campus and beyond forging multidisciplinary teams and partnerships. The SCS uses the Gulf of Mexico, the state of Texas, and the Houston and Galveston region as research models.
The Shell Center for Sustainability's mission is to foster an interdisciplinary program of research, outreach, and education to address actions that can be taken to ensure the sustainable development of communities' living standards, interpreted broadly, to encompass all factors affecting the overall quality of life.
Information from http://shellcenter.rice.edu/Content.aspx?id=52
Content Description
This collection contains the administrative files, meeting minutes and records, publications, audio/visual (DVDs) presentations, and reports for the Rice University Shell Center for Sustainability.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection open for research without restrictions, except for certain materials in the Finance sub-series and the Human Resources sub-series, which are restricted from all viewing and use until 2050.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred by Lilibeth Andre in 2017.
Index Terms
Subjects
Sustainable development; Research; Universities and colleges
Document Types
minutes (administrative records)
Places
Rice University
Subjects (Persons)
Andre, Lilibeth
- Series I. Administrative Files
  - Background Materials (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Shell Center proposal (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Inaugural Conference, 2003-03-12-2003-03-13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Committee Meetings - Management and Operational
    - Briefing Book - Management and Operating Committee Meeting, 2003-12-15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Management and Operating Committee Meeting, 2003-12-15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Briefing Book - Management and Operating Committee(2 folders), 2004-09-24 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - Management and Operating Committee Meeting (2 folders), 2004-09-24 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - Management Committee Meeting, 2009-2012 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Operating Committee Meetings, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Operating Committee Meeting Records (3 folders), 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 12-14)
    - Operating Committee Meeting records, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Operating Committee, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Operating Committee Meetings and Minutes (2 folders), 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
    - Operating Committee Meeting and Minutes (2 folders), 2010-2013 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
    - Operating Committee Meeting and Minutes, 2014-2015, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Events
    - Air and Urban Sustainability workshop, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Air Quality in Houston: Seminar Series, Fall 2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Air Monitoring Seminar transcript, 2003-10-07 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Air Quality in Houston: panel transcript, 2003-11-13 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Air Quality in Houston summary (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Air Quality in Houston: Executive summary, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - China and sustainable development, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Sustainable Development in the Energy Industry, 2004-08-05 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Hot Air Topics Conference - research, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Hot Air Topics conference, 2004-10-07 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Hot Air Topics Conference - websites (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Particulate Matter Seminars (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Climate Change Conference, 2005-02 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Houston's Air Research conference, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Climate Change conference, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Eco-marathon, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Shell-Rice alumni reception, 2010-04-06 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Tunafest, 2010-07 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Shell center "meet and greet", 2010-12-01 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Sustainability Pay$ - the Copenhagen Experience, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Sustainable Indicators conference, 2011-02 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Blue Ribbon Resilient Communities, 2011-06-28 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - State of the Gulf of Mexico Summit, 2011-12-04 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Pathways to Urban Sustainability, 2012-01 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Gulf Coastal Science Consortium workshop, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Fall workshop, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Penrose/Chapman Conference, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Powering Progress Together Forum, 2013-04 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Sustainable Development of Houston Districts, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Shell Country Chair Partners Forum, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Coastal Response Conference, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - U.S. Social Investment Partners Forum, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - People and Nature Conference, 2015-10 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Carbon 2065 workshop, 2015-10 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Energy and Environment task force, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Humans in Space Symposium, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Finance
    - Budget 2007-2015 (2 folders) - [restricted] (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
    - Budget 2009-2010 - [restricted] (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Budget 2010 - [restricted] (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Development Funds 2007-2011 - [restricted] (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Funding Opportunities (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Grants matrix (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Human Resources
    - Executive Director - Christian Holmes, 2003-2005
      - Zygourakis, Kyriacos, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Epstein, Marc - publications (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - National Council for Science and the Environment, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - University of Houston correspondence, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - WBCSD, 2003-05-07 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Background Materials: Royal Dutch Shell/Group of Companies, Organization and Approach to Sustainability (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Petroleum Equipment Suppliers Association Meeting, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - China Business Council for Sustainable Development (CBCSD), 2004 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Renewable Energy and Energy Efficiency Partnership meeting, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Nankai Initative, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - EESI/Shell Center for Sustainability review committee meeting, 2005-02-11 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Briefing for EESI - Shell Center Review Committee, 2005-04-28 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Research plans and priorities, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Hartley, Peter - Academic Director (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Lilibeth Andre - Associate Director
      - SCS Advisors' Board (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Communication - Shell - Griffin, Claude (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Communication - Shell - Others (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Corporate Council Meeting, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 2008-2013 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Events, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Events: Workshop retreat, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Events: proposed, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Events: Audobon, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Events: CC Fall, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Events: Co-sponsored (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Events: Registrations (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Events: Venues (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Events: Fall workshop, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Rice Centers roundtable, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Sponsorships (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Technical Review Board (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Texas Commission on Environmental Quality, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Travel - San Luis Potosi, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Visitors, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Candidates for Director [restricted], 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Executive Director - job description [restricted] (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Sustainable Indicator post-doc applicants [restricted] (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - King, Lester - post-doc application [restricted] (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Interns - Hiring Guidelines (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Interns, 2008-2012 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Interns 2010-2011 (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 41-42)
    - Interns - Fall 2010 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Interns Summer 2011 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Interns Spring 2012 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Interns Fall 2012 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Interns 2014 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Interns 2016 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Media
    - SCS Communications Plan (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Media Clips, 2002-2011 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Media Public Affairs, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Press Releases, 2011-2013 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Print Media (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Promotional flier, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Shell Center poster, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Promotional opportunities (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - SCS Media Report (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Meeting Drafts (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Meetings: Internal Strategy (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Meetings: Planning (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Meeting: Montgomery County proposal, 2007-06-25 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - SCS Overview, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Speaker Requests (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - SCS Video project, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Video Editing (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Video Inventory (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Video - Nanoparticles Monitoring script, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Web experts directory (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Web procedure (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Web research 2006 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Web Services, 2010-2012 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Reports
    - Shell Center: Year End report, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Shell Center: Year End report, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Briefing for John Hofmeister, 2005-04 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Status Report, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Shell Center: Year End report, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report 2008 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report 2010 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report 2011 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report 2012 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report 2014 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Strategic Plan
    - Strategic Plan, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Strategic Plan, 2003-2008 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Strategic Plan draft, 2005-08-10 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Strategic Plan Status Report, 2005-08-11 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Plan 2009-10 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Strategic Plan, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Strategic Plan 2012-13 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Strategic Plan 2015 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Series II. Projects
  - 2003
    - Requests for Proposals, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Pinedale Conservation Planning, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Pinedale Research Project (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Pinedale Analysis (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 2004
    - Houston Sustainability Scenarios Project (4 folders) (Box 4, Folder 24-27)
  - 2005
    - Clean Air Act Implementation in Houston: A Historical Perspective 1970-2005 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Clean Air research (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Houston and Clean Air: the state implementation plan (SIP) (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - SIP Conference, 2005-02-24 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 2006
    - Rice University Biodiesel Initiative (RUBI) (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Invasive Plant Abundance (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - K-12 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Future (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Biodiversity (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Business (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Coastal Cities (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Gas Hydrates (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Ozone Research (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Center for Environmental Remediation and Sustainable Development (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Research (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - 2007
    - COHAN Biofuels (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Cohan-Integrated Economic (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Masiello (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Monitoring Engineered Nanoparticles in the Environment (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Water Footprint of Biofuels (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Research Project PIs (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Project Reviewers (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Submissions (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Other Projects (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 2008
    - Long-Range Sustainability Plan for the Upper Texas Coast (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Genetic and Environmental Impacts (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Understanding Mercury Chemistry in the Atmosphere of Houston (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Low-cost Solar Thermal collectors (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Capteur Soleil and Social Enterprise (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Measuring the Societal Benefits of Hazardous Waste Site Cleanups (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Project Proposals (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Non-selected proposals (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 2009
    - Water Infrastructure for Improving Public Health (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Response of Native plant mating systems (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Rice Solar Decathlon Team (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Reducing energy use and carbon dioxide (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Bio-inspired Hierarchical Surfaces (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Project proposals (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Requests for Proposals (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 2010
    - Lifeline Sustainability (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Houston Urban Bayous Sampling (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Rice Solar Car 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Semiconducting Particle and Conjugated Polymer Nanocomposites (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Understanding Religious Tradition and Caring for the Environment (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Computational guidance of efficient CO2 fixation (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Linking climate change to the structure (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Measuring City Sustainability: Project Houston - Phase II (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Measuring City Sustainability Report, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Request for Proposals, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - 2011
    - Houston Sustainability Indicators (HSI) Project
      - Indicators: Sustainable Development (2 folders), 2011 (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
      - Intern, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Outreach (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Report (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Workshops (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Workshop: Social Development, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Workshop series, 2012-10 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Workshop: Economics, 2012-10 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Workshop: Environment, 2012-10 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Web Services, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - The Petropolis of Tomorrow (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Developing Performance Metrics for Evaluating Social Impacts (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Measurement of Atmosphere Particle Number Concentrations in Houston (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Self-Sustained Portable Capacitive Deionization (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Effects of anthropogenic nutrient enrichment (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Solar - Thermal Powered Autoclave (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - High Performance Polymer Photovoltaics (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Request for Proposals, 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - 2012-2013
    - Water, Nutrients and Sustainability (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Stress Nexus of Coastlines (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Sustainable Development of Houston Districts: the health of the city/Executive Summary, 2013-06 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Zero Carbon Development (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Request for Faculty Proposals (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - 2014-2016
    - Natural Gas Leakage in Urban Houston (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Dynamic Modeling of the Nitrogen Cycle of Biochar-amended Soils (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Risk and Resilience along Houston's Ship Channel (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Projects 2016 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Request for Faculty Proposals (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Gulf Research Program/National Science Foundation Proposal, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Other Projects
    - EPA: Houston Air Research, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Energy and Water Sustainability Course, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Proposed Events, 2011
    - Continuing Studies - Sustainability Management, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Restore Act: Centers for Excellence, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - K-12 Iniative (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Masters' Program Natural Science brochure (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Rice Masters' Programs Sustainability (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Series III. Rice University
  - Center for Studies of Environment and Society (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Centennial Campaign Social Sciences 2009 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - De Lange Conference: Sustainability of Houston, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - De Lange Conference: Seeking the Humane Metropolis: Ecologies for the future, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - De Lange Conference: the Future of a Research University in a Global Age, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Energy and Environmental Systems Institute, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Engagement with Rice University, 2012-2013 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - International Visiting Fellows Program (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Kinder Institute, 2015-2017 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Rice Alliance - Shell Sustainability Award, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Rice Environmental Society (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Rice Policies (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Rice Undergraduate Research Symposium, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Rice Undergraduate Research Symposium, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Rice Undergraduate Tech Challenge, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - SSPEED report: Learning the Lessons of Hurricane Ike, 2010-05 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Professional Masters' program (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Student papers (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 31-32)
- Series IV. Non-Rice organizations
  - BP: Global Warming: the problem and potential solutions (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Center for Houston's Future, 2007-2014 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Citizens' Environmental Coalition: Environmental Resource Guides, 2013, 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - City of Houston. Houston Police Department. "Aerial FLIR System Aids in the Detection of Illegal Discharges into the Houston Ship Channel Area", 2004-05-07 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - GEMI: Global Environmental Health and Safety Excellence (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Imperial College Centre for Energy Policy and Technology, 2002-12-20 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - National Association of Environmental Professionals (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - National Council for Science and the Environment (NCSE) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - National Research Council Implementing Climate and Global Change (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Pew Energy Strategy: U.S. Energy Scenarios for the 21st century, 2003-07 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Pollution Prevention Advisory Committee - Texas Commission on Environmental Quality (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 43-44)
  - Shell: New Lens Scenarios, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - United States Business Council for Sustainable Development, 2004-06 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - World Environmental Center (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Series V. Digital Materials (Box 7)
  - Air Quality in Houston - Fall 2003: Regulatory Issues (3 copies) DVD
  - Air Quality in Houston - Fall 2003: Health Effects (3 copies) DVD
  - Air Quality in Houston - Fall 2003: Air Monitoring (3 copies) DVD
  - Air Quality in Houston - Fall 2003: Modeling (3 copies) DVD
  - America's Energy Coast DVD
  - The Arctic on the Fast Track of Change DVD, 2012-04-20
  - Carbon 2065: Session 1 DVD
  - Carbon 2065: Session 2 DVD
  - Carbon 2065: Session 3 DVD
  - China & Sustainable Development DVD, 2004-09-27
  - Climate Change: Magnitude of the Problem DVD, 2004-09-27
  - Earth 2050: The Future of Energy DVD, 2011
  - Figures 1-8 DVD
  - Houston Air Conference - Module 1 & 2 (2 copies) DVD, 2008-10-16
  - Houston Air Conference - Module 3 & 4 (2 copies) DVD, 2008-10-16
  - Houston Air Conference - Module 5 (3 copies) DVD, 2008-10-16
  - Houston Air Quality Fall 2004 Seminars: Part One DVD
  - Houston Air Quality Fall 2004 Seminars: Part Two DVD
  - Houston Air Quality Fall 2004 Seminars: Part Four DVD
  - Houston Community Sustainability Symposium & Mixer DVD, 2014-03-26
  - Houston Water Conference 2009 - Sessions 1 & 2 DVD
  - Houston Water Conference 2009 - Sessions 3 & 4 DVD
  - Houston Water Conference 2009 - Sessions 5 DVD
  - How Sustainable is the Texas Coast: Are we in a "state of denial?" (2 copies) DVD, 2014-10-29
  - The State of the Gulf: America's Sea DVD
  - Iceland Ice Sheet DVD
  - I-Sweep 2008 (3 copies) DVD
  - I-Sweep 2008: Photos CD-R
  - I-Sweep 2009 DVD
  - Landscan PowerPoint DVD, 2004-04-02
  - The Long Thaw DVD, 2011-03-08
  - Odebrecht Award for Sustainable Development DVD, 2012
  - "Shell" CD-R, 2007-08
  - "Shell" CD-R, 2007-06
  - Shell Roughcut DVD, 2010-05-24
  - SCS DV file DVD-R, 2011-04-12
  - SCS: Houston Air Quality PowerPoint CD, 2004-11-09
  - SCS: Research and Opportunities DVD, 2009-02-19
  - SCS: Video in progress DVD, 2011-03-17
  - SCS video DVD, 2011-03-31
  - SCS video DVD, 2011-03-22
  - SCS Video Rough Cut 2 DVD, 2010-05-20
  - SCS: version 6 DVD, 2010-06-22
  - SCS: Rough Cut 4 DVD, 2010-06-11
  - SCS: BRC 1, 2 DVD, 2013-10-09
  - SCS: BRC 3 DVD, 2013-10-09
  - SCS: RMC 1, 2, 3 DVD, 2013-10-08
  - The Sustainable Development of Houston Districts: The Health of the City (2 copies) DVD, 2013-10-08
  - Sustainability Pay$: The Copenhagen Experience, Parts 1-2 DVD
  - Sustainability Pay$: The Copenhagen Experience - Lunch Session (3 copies) DVD
  - Texas Water Spring 2004 Seminars: Flooding and Watershed Management DVD
  - Texas Water Spring 2004 Seminars: Water Supply DVD
  - Traveling the Shore of the Spanish Sea CD-R, 2009-04-10